myvega.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Vega (US)

### MyVega & VegaSport Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Vega web site(s) owned (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise) or controlled by Sequel Natural Ltd. d/b/a Vega or any of its related, affiliated or subsidiary companies (“Company,” “Vega ,” “we,” “our” or “us”) or other interactive features that are accessible or downloadable through the web sites owned or controlled by Company and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Web Sites”). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Web Sites, and does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by Company (unless specifically stated). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect on the Web Sites, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you may have regarding our collection, use, and disclosure of such information.

Vega is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our Web Site. We take this matter very seriously, and have instituted practices to ensure that none of your privacy rights as stated herein are ever violated. The following outlines Vega ‘s privacy policy and details the measures we have taken to safeguard and protect your privacy, while providing you with a unique and rewarding online shopping experience. By visiting the Web Sites, you are agreeing to the policies detailed below.

### What information does Vega collect?

In order to serve you better, Vega collects and stores your personal information when you: (i) create an account on myvega.com; (ii) sign up to be notified of special deals like discounts and exclusive offers. When creating an account, we ask you for your first and last name, your e-mail address, a password, and perhaps some other similar information.

### What does Vega do with this personal information?

Your information is used to process personalize your experience on the Web Sites, for internal purposes and to comply with any legal requirements. By storing your personal information on a secure server, Vega is able to shorten your login process and allow you modify your personal profile online.

### How does Vega safeguard my personal information?

Vega has implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights and is not shared with any other parties. When you access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information supplied by you is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and securely stored in Vega database.

### Does Vega provide a way to update or remove personal information?

Vega provides a “My Account” feature on our website which allows you to modify and/or remove most of your personal information. This page can be accessed by clicking the “My Account” link at the top of every page on the site. The information contained within “My Account” is secure and accessible only by you or authorized Vega personnel.

### Does Vega use “cookies”?

Yes. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer’s browser. The cookie holds information a site may need to personalize your experience and to gather website statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the internet provider’s domain name and country that our visitors come from (e.g. “aol.com” or “msn.com”) and the addresses of the sites visited immediately before coming to and immediately after the Web Sites. However, none of this information is associated with you as an individual. It is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate. The information in the cookies lets us trace your “click stream” activity (i.e., the paths take by visitors to our site as they move from page to page). Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you.  
To browse without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access most of the features on Vega.

### How does Vega use my e-mail address?

Your e-mail address is used to create and identify your account on myvega.com. Your e-mail address is also used by Vega to correspond with you about the Vega Program. We will also include you in our Vega e-newsletter list to keep you updated on news and specials. You may opt out of this at any time at the bottom of any email newsletter sent to you.  
Alternately, if you have created an account with Vega, you can also remove your email address from our list of addresses that receive information about new products, service, sales and promotions by clicking on the “my account” button that appears on most every page of our website, logging into your account, clicking on the “edit preferences” button, and making the appropriate change.

### How can you remove your name from our direct mail or email list?

To have your email address removed from our list of addresses that receive information about new products, service, sales and promotions, simply click on the “Unsubscribe” link that appears at the bottom of any email and follow the simple instructions. Alternately, if you have created an account with Vega, you can also remove your email address from our list of addresses that receive information about new products, service, sales and promotions by clicking on the “my account” button that appears on most every page of our Web site, logging into your account, clicking on the “edit preferences” button, and making the appropriate change.

### Your consent

You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of the terms of service and you agree that using the Web Site signifies your assent to Vega’s privacy policy. Vega reserves the right to change the terms of service, including this privacy policy, at any time, without advanced notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances.

### With whom information may be shared

Except as otherwise disclosed at the time you provide your information, the following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others:

### Third parties providing services on our behalf

We may employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf; examples include hosting or operating Web Sites, fulfilling orders for products and services purchased through the Web Sites, sending e-mail and/or other communications, providing wireless services, removing repetitive information from customer lists, data analysis, marketing assistance, credit card payment processing, and customer service. These third parties may have access to your personal information for the purpose of performing such functions on the Web Sites’ behalf.

### Non-Personal Information

We may share non-personal information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and web site usage information with third parties.

### Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions through the Web Sites that may require registration. If you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion, your personal information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion.

### Business Transfers

Company may share the information collected through the Web Sites with and among the Web Sites, and may share the information with its subsidiaries and affiliates. Company or any of it assets, including the Web Sites, may be sold, or other transactions may occur in which your personal information is one of the key business assets for the transaction. In such a case, your personal information may be one of the business assets we transfer. Hence, Company reserves the right to disclose and transfer user information, including personal information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our assets, or other corporate change.

### Legal Protections and Law Enforcement

We may disclose information about our users, including your personal information, in the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or other valid law enforcement measures; to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Web Sites and applicable laws; or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of the Web Sites, our users or others. We may also use Device Identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, internet service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

### Security

Company incorporates reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, or wireless transmission, or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company via its Web Sites, and you do so at your own risk.
